Attack of the Hollywood Clichés! is a documentary film directed by Sean Doherty.
One-man armies, meet-cutes, casual strolls away from huge explosions — stars and
industry insiders toast and roast these cinematic chestnuts and more.
Self - Host / Narrator (voice), played by Rob Lowe.
Self - Screenwriter, played by John August.
Self - Comedian, played by Sanjeev Bhaskar.
Self - Broadcaster, played by Anna Bogutskaya.
Self - Broadcaster, played by Jess Cagle.
Self - Film Critic, played by David Edelstein.
The Rip is a 2026 American action thriller film written and directed by
Joe Carnahan who developed the story with Michael McGrale.
The film stars Matt Damon and Ben Affleck as police officers within
the narcotics unit of the Miami-Dade Police Department.
It also stars Steven Yeun, Teyana Taylor, Sasha Calle, Catalina
Sandino Moreno, Scott Adkins, and Kyle Chandler.
The film is inspired by the true story of
Miami-Dade County Sheriff Chris Casiano.
This film tells the story of a group of police officers who, during a raid on a hidden cash operation, find
their trust broken down as team members suspect each other of trying to steal a large sum of cash.
It was released by Netflix on January 16, 2026, to
generally favorable reviews from critics.
The production company, Artist Equity, negotiated a first of its kind deal with Netflix that provides the workers
involved in the production of the film with a bonus if it performs well on the streaming platform.
The film explores themes of cinema on cinema, movie business, filmmaking.